- 喔 嘿 乔伊   - 嗯
- Oh, hey, Joey.    - Mmm.
- 你好   - 听着 我有件事要问你
- Hey.    - Listen, I need to ask you something.
你知道我继父在坐牢
You know how my stepdad's in prison?
- 知道   - 好
- Yeah.    - Yeah.
本来周末他可以放假 来参加明天的婚礼
He was supposed to get a weekend furlough so he could go to the wedding.
可是他刚刚打电话来…
But he just called and...
看来刺杀其他犯人的活动 不能等到星期一才办
Well, apparently stabbing Iceman in the exercise yard couldn't wait till Monday.
- 所以他不能来？ - 对
- So he can't come?    - No.
所以没有人陪我走过走道 然后…
And so there's no one to walk me down the aisle. And...
如果你能陪我 我会很开心
Well, I would just really love it if you would do it.
- 你说真的？ - 当然
- Seriously?    - Yeah.
你待我就跟父亲一样
You've, you know, sort of been like a dad to me.
我是说 你一直很照顾我 也常和我分享生活智慧
You've always, you know, looked out for me and shared your wisdom.
我的确很有"雅慧"
I am pretty "wisdomous."
你愿意吗？
So, what do you say?
你开玩笑吗？菲比 这是我的荣幸
Are you kidding? Phoebe, I would be honored.
谢谢
PHOEBE: Oh, thank you.
我希望…
I hope...
我希望你了解 你对我有多重要
I hope you know how much you mean to me.
听着 我也希望…
Listen, I hope...
我也希望你知道…
I hope that you know...
不能让你看见老爸哭 回房间去
I don't want you to see your father cry. Go to your room!
- 哦   - 不必了…老爸请客
- Oh.    - Oh, no, no, no. Let your dad get this.
又是我的婚礼策划人 她快把我搞疯了
Oh. It's my wedding planner. She's driving me crazy!
喂？不要尖叫
Hello? Okay, stop screaming!
好 那就比目鱼
Okay, so halibut.
好 那就换鲑鱼 随便 我不知道…
All right, so salmon. Either way. I don't...
- 我不在乎   - 可是我在乎
- It doesn't matter to me.    - Well, it matters to me!
我不在乎 你选就好
Well, I don't care. So you pick.
你刚刚挂我电话吗？
Did you just hang up on me?
听着 我要你在1800时 到晚餐预演
All right, look, I need you at the rehearsal dinner tonight at 1800 hours.
好…那是几点？
Okay. What time is that?
你听不懂军事时间代码？
You don't know military time?
那天我正好在接受导弹训练
I must have been in missile training the day they taught that.
减掉12
Just subtract 12.
好 1800减12…
Okay, so 1800 minus 12...
就是1788
...is 1788.
- 六点   - 好
- Six o'clock!    - Okay.
等等…我是盖勒
Hold on. Yeah? Geller here.
不 我说四点就要送达 再见
No, I said it has to be there by 4:00. Goodbye.
做个冰雕是有多难？
How hard is it to make an ice sculpture?
冰雕？这样太隆重了
That sounds really fancy.
我说只要简单的婚礼就好
I told you, I just want a simple wedding.
拜托 甜心 细节交给我就好
Please, honey, leave the details to me.
我会竭尽所能让你感到宾至如归
Now, I wanna make this day as special for you as I can.
我想让竖琴师穿白色
I was thinking the harpist should wear white.
竖琴师？我朋友玛洁莉 不是要打钢鼓？
Harpist? My friend Marjorie is playing the steel drums.
- 她退出了   - 真的？为什么？
- Oh, she backed out.    - She did? Why?
我逼她的
I made her.
钢鼓并不适合典雅的婚礼
Steel drums don't really say "elegant wedding."
- 还有玛洁莉浓郁的体味   - 听好
- Nor does Marjorie's overwhelming scent.     - Hey!
等西藏独立后 她自然会洗澡
She will shower when Tibet is free.
- 嘿 你看起来真美   - 你也不错
- Hey. You look great.    - You too.
很高兴能来晚餐彩排 很少有机会用赛前先试吃
I'm glad we're having a rehearsal dinner. I rarely practice my meals before I eat.
你忘记你要送我们的礼物了吗？
What did we say was your one gift to us?
不说冷笑话 可是不是要等正式婚礼再说？
No stupid jokes, but I thought that was for the actual wedding.
先彩排
Rehearse it.
你好
Hi.
- 谢谢你们来   - 对…
- Thanks for coming, you guys.    - Oh, yeah...
我本来…要跟你握手的
I was... I was going for a handshake.
所以你的手抵住我的胯下？
That why your hand's against my crotch?
- 没错   - 好
- That is why.    - Yeah.
瑞秋 艾玛在哪？
So, Rach, where's Emma?
摩妮卡逼我把她托我妈带
Monica made me send her to my mom's.
因为小婴儿不适合参加婚礼
Apparently, babies and weddings don't mix.
你还在为那死小鬼抱怨吗？
Are you still crying about your damn baby?
菲比 你要让队伍继续动 切记 一人二十秒
Pheebs, you got to keep the line moving. Remember, 20 seconds per person.
这些小丑 你每天都见得到
You see these clowns all the time.
- 你们是麦克的父母 对吧？ - 是的
- Hey, you're Mike's parents, right?    - Yes, we are.
孩子们长得真快 不是吗？
Gosh, our little ones are growing up fast, aren't they?
- 什么意思？ - 你知道的…
- How's that?    - You know...
虽然很替他们高兴 但要放手却也很难
...on one hand, you're happy for them. On the other, it's hard to let go.
你到底是谁？
Who in God's name are you?
我也不是很喜欢你 老兄 我是看在孩子的份上给你面子
I'm not that fond of you either, buddy. I'm just trying to be nice for the kids.
对了 我们还不知道 明天在婚礼中要负责的工作
You know what? We have no idea what we're doing in the wedding tomorrow.
我们应该要当伴郎的 怎么还不跟我们说？
I thought we'd be groomsmen. They would have asked us by now.
他们什么时候请你当伴娘的？
When did they ask you to be a bridesmaid?
- 11月   - 看来情况不妙
- November.    - I wanna say it's not looking good.
- 菲比？ - 怎么了？
- Hey, Pheebs?    - Huh?
你还没分配他们在婚礼的工作
You haven't told these guys what they're doing in the wedding yet.
这个…他们不必参与婚礼的工作
Um, well, they're not in the wedding.
什么？
What?
那么…
Well...
好尴尬
...this is really awkward.
对了 我可以离开
Oh, and I can leave.
抱歉 两位 麦克有哥哥和同学
I'm sorry, you guys. But Mike's got his brother and his friends from school.
所以你们…
So, you know, you were...
其实 你们是备取 差一点就当成了
If it helps, you were next in line. You just missed the cut.
天啊
Oh, man.
这像是花式溜冰队的噩梦又重演了
This is like figure skating team all over again.
我是说水上芭蕾
I mean, synchronized swimming.
我是说…平衡木
I mean... I mean, the balance beam.
- 救救我   - 美式足球
- Help me.     - Football.
感谢你
Thank you.
菲比 快吐出来 里面有猪肉
Oh, Pheebs, spit that out. That has pork in it.
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!
我以为锅贴不是素食的吗？
I thought the pot stickers were supposed to be vegetarian?
对 我换掉了 我有传真通知你
Yeah, I changed them. I sent you a fax about it.
我没有传真机
I don't have a fax machine.
那么接下来会有更多惊喜
Huh. Well, then there are gonna be a few surprises.
想不到我们是唯一 无法参与婚礼工作的人
I can't believe we're gonna be the only people not in the wedding.
- 我了解 我讨厌遭到冷落   - 更何况是婚礼
- I know. I hate being left out of things.    - And it's a wedding.
我没份才真是诡异
It'll be weird if I'm not in it.
- 各位 你们好吗？ - 很好
- Hey, guys, how's it going?    - Fine.
我们闲着没事坐在这儿 为明天要做的事彩排
We're sitting here, alone, doing nothing. It's our rehearsal for tomorrow.
听着 关于明天我有件事要问你们
Look, about tomorrow, I've got a question for you.
我刚发现 其中一个伴郎有急事不能来
I found out one of my groomsmen had an emergency and can't make it.
- 出了什么事？ - 谁管他？然后呢？
- What happened?     - Who cares? And?
我在想也许你们其中一个人…
And I was wondering if one of you guys...
- 我来   - 我要
- I'll do it!    - Me!
你们都想当？可是只有一个空缺
You both wanna do it? There's only room for one.
选我 我穿礼服很帅 但不会抢走你们的风采
Pick me. I look great in a tux, and I won't steal focus.
不…麦克 应该选我 你瞧
No, Mike. No, no, you wanna pick me. I mean... Watch.
哈？
Huh?
我觉得由我决定不太妥当
You know, I really don't feel very comfortable making this decision.
菲比跟你们比较熟 我请她选好了
You know, Phoebe knows you better. I'm gonna let her choose.
如果让菲比选 那就见过麦克的新伴郎吧
Well, if Phoebe's choosing, then say hello to Mike's next groomsman.
当然 可是我需要镜子…
Oh, I will. But I will need a mirror...
因为就是在下
...as he is me.
- 得了吧 你死定了   - 你才死透了
- Please. You're going down.    - You are going "downer."
花式溜冰队的人都这么说话吗？
They say that on the figure skating team?
我不知道 我根本没入选
I wouldn't know. I didn't make it.
你知道我明天要 代替菲比的继父吧？
You know I'm filling in for Phoebe's stepdad tomorrow, right?
- 对 感谢你的帮忙   - 我乐意之至
- Yeah. Yeah. Hey, thanks for doing that.    - Oh, hey, my pleasure.
你对我的菲比有何意图？
So, what are your intentions with my Phoebe?
- 我意图娶她为妻   - 耍嘴皮子
- I intend to marry her.    - Oh, a wiseacre.
我还听说你打算以弹钢琴维持家计？
I understand you plan to support your wife by playing the piano?
这样收入不会不稳定吗？
Isn't that kind of unstable?
- 应该比演戏好   - 两好球
- No more so than acting.    - Strike two.
你说得对 可能要她养我
You're right. She probably will support me.
不如搬去和你住吧？爸
Hey, unless we move in with you, Dad.
三好球
Strike three.
你只剩一次机会 麦克
You only get one more, Mike.
你决定如何？
So? What did you decide?
我决定去上厕所
I decided to pee.
麦克没跟你说吗？你得从我们之中 选出一个人参加婚礼
You have to choose one of us to be in your wedding.
- 有一个伴郎不能来   - 不行…
- One of the groomsmen fell out.     - Oh, no, no.
我不能从你们俩选择 我爱你们俩
I can't choose between you two. I love you both so much.
所以我们原本才不能参与婚礼
Just not enough to put us in the original wedding party.
可是我不想选 这…
But I don't wanna choose. It's...
- 等等 瑞秋？ - 什么？
- Okay, wait. Rach?    - Yeah?
听着 我有个伴娘的特殊任务 要交给你
Listen, I have a very special bridesmaid task for you to do.
太好了 是什么？
Goody! What is it?
现在有一个伴郎的空缺
Well, there's a spot open for only one groomsman...
你要从罗斯和钱德其中择一 祝你好运
...and you have to choose between Ross and Chandler. So good luck with that.
什么…？我不想选
What? What, what, what? No, I don't wanna do that.
看来我得找新伴娘了
I guess I have to find a new bridesmaid.
我来当
I'll do it!
现在已经2100了
Okay, it's 2100 hours.
- 该敬酒了   - 我可以去上厕所吗？
- Time for your toast.    - Do I have time to go to the bathroom?
你在2030有上厕所时间 请遵守时间表 麦克
You had a bathroom break at 2030. Pee on your own time, Mike.
敬酒致词要简短
In regards to the toasts, okay, you wanna keep them short.
冗长致词是晚餐彩排的一大杀手
Nothing kills a rehearsal dinner like long speeches. Okay.
只要进去办完正事就出来
You just get in, do your thing, and get out.
你对钱德都这么说吗？
Is that what you say to Chandler?
已经2101了 我并不高兴
It's 2101, and I am not amused.
好的
Okay.
新郎新娘有几句话要说
The bride and groom have a few words they'd like to say.
各位 大家好
Okay. Hello, everyone.
感谢各位今晚的到来 明天就是大喜之日了
And thank you all for being here tonight. So tomorrow's the big event.
有些人也许不知道麦克和我 一开始并没有看对眼
Some of you might not know, but Mike and I didn't get off to the best start.
对 我朋友乔伊和我…
Yeah. My friend Joey and I...
本来想替对方介绍对象 所以我…
...decided to fix each other up with friends. So I...
好吧 我…
Oh, okay. I...
所以我把他介绍给我朋友玛莉艾伦
I thought about it, and I fixed him up with my friend Mary Ellen...
她今晚不必前来 因为…其实…
...who couldn't be here tonight, because... It's not...
其实不重要 她人在戒毒中心
It's not important. Well, she's in rehab.
总之 乔伊说要把他朋友 麦克介绍给我
Anyway. So Joey said that he was fixing me up with his friend Mike...
可是他没有叫麦克的朋友 所以借用我的麦克
...only he didn't have a friend Mike, so he just brought my Mike. And... And...
然后…
Then...
但结果…却是好的
But despite, you know... It got good.
我想趁此机会谈我无法到来的母亲
I wanna take a moment to mention my mother, who couldn't be here.
天啊
Oh, God.
机会没了
And... And moment's over.
好…这个跳过
So okay... Oh, no, forget that.
这也跳过…这个好笑
I can forget that. Oh, this is funny.
可是要先说这个才听得懂
Oh, but you need to know that to get that.
那么…好…
So... Oh, well, okay.
我…好…
I... Okay.
摩妮卡 我受不了了
Okay, Monica, I can't do it like this!
这是我的婚礼好吗？我不要这个…
This is my wedding, okay? I don't want this...
或是这掴…还有这个…
Or this... Or this...
可以吗？我只要一个简单的婚礼
Okay? I just wanted a simple wedding...
而且我的未婚夫 随时想上厕所都可以
...where my fiancé can go to the bathroom any time he wants!
- 算了 我不要你了   - 什么？
- You know what? You're done.    - What?
你被炒鱿鱼了
You're fired!
干杯
Cheers.
- 嘿   - 大喜之日快乐
- Hey.    - Happy wedding day.
祝你我的大喜之日快乐
Happy my wedding day to you.
乔伊 这里要当伴娘休息室
Joey, listen, this is gonna be bridesmaid central, all right?
所以厕所里会有人梳发 上化妆品
We're gonna have hair and makeup in the bathroom.
我空出冰箱一些空间放胸花
I had to move a couple things in the fridge to make room for the corsages.
可恶 早知道有胸花吃 我就不吃早餐了
Man! I wouldn't have had breakfast if I knew there was gonna be corsages.
嗨
Hi.
关于昨晚…
About last night...
我知道你压力很大…
I know you're under a lot of stress, and...
虽然你的话有点伤人…
Well, even though the things you said hurt me a little bit...
我的重点是…
My point is...
我希望你让我继续工作
Well, I'm willing to take my job back.
没关系
Oh, well, that's okay.
我觉得你只当伴娘 你我会处得比较好
I think you and I will do much better if you're just here as a bridesmaid.
是这样吗？
Oh, is that so?
好吧
Okay.
既然如此 拿去
If that's really what you want, then here.
耳机给你 但是我不想给你耳机
I give you the headset. I don't really wanna give you the headset.
既然你要自己处理 那就要回复这些留言
I guess if you're taking over, then you should probably return these messages.
- 这么多   -  额
- This is a lot.    - Uh-huh.
我相信你可以应付 虽然我的组织能力
But I'm sure you can handle this. I have won awards...
曾经得过奖 但我相信你应付得来
...for my organizational skills. But I'm sure you'll do fine.
- 你得过奖？ - 我全都用电脑列印出来
- You've won awards?    - I printed them out on my computer.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.    - Hi.
- 瑞秋在哪？ - 房间里 怎么了？
- Where's Rach?    - She's in her room. Why?
我要跟她谈伴郎的事
I have to talk to her about this groomsman situation.
我不要像呆瓜一样坐在那看着钱德
I'm not gonna watch Chandler up there while I'm in the seats like some chump.
老天啊 你真是明艳动人
My God, you're breathtaking.
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
你不会已经选出伴郎人选了吧？
You haven't by any chance chosen a groomsman yet, have you?
罗斯 不要再给我压力了
Ross, please don't make this harder than it already is.
我不会 我让你轻松点 选我就好
I'm not. I'm making it easier. Pick me.
- 钱德也说这对他意义重大   - 听我说…
- Chandler said it's important to him too.    - Listen. Listen.
你选的人将会陪你走向走道
Whoever you pick is gonna walk down the aisle with you.
我保证不会说话 可是如果你选钱德
Now, I promise I won't say a word. But if you pick Chandler...
他会不停在你耳边说冷笑话
...he's gonna be whispering stupid jokes in your ear the whole time.
两个烂苹果 你比较不烂
Oh, you are the lesser of two evils.
太好了
Yes!
史文 我听不懂你的话 你说花怎么了？
Sven, I don't understand what you're saying. What is wrong with the flowers?
"烂话"？"烂话"到底是什么？
"Lorkins"? What the hell are "lorkins"?
我知道
I know.
- 你们好   - 麦克 如果你是瑞典人
- Hey.    - Mike, if you were Swedish...
然后你说"烂话" 那会是什么花？
...and you were saying the word "lorkins," what flower would that be?
- 兰花？ - 没错
- Orchids?    - Right there!
难怪我要嫁给你
That's why I'm marrying you.
你好 麦克
Hello, Michael.
乔瑟夫
Joseph.
借一步说话好吗？
May I have a word with you, please?
这里真…
This is...
不错
...great.
请坐
Have a seat.
昨晚…
Last night...
我试着欢迎你加入我的家族
...I tried to welcome you into my family.
反之 你却不尊重我
And instead, you disrespect me.
此举我绝不允许
I cannot allow this.
你在为一部烂黑帮电影彩排吗？
Are you rehearsing for some really bad Mafia movie?
又给我回嘴
More back talk.
没错 我的确引用最近 失败的试镜台词
And yes, I may be borrowing a few lines from my recent unsuccessful audition...
《家族荣耀2:打开天窗说亮话》
...for Family Honor 2: This A-Time It's A-Personal.
乔伊 我今天有点忙 你到底要说什么？
Joey, I kind of have a lot to do today. What do you want?
我要你认真看待此事
I want you to take this seriously!
菲比对我而言非常重要
Phoebe is very, very important to me, okay?
我要确定你能照顾她
I wanna make sure you are gonna take care of her.
乔伊 我爱菲比
Joe, I love Phoebe.
她是我一生最重要的人
She's the most important thing in my life.
我死也不会让她受伤害
I'd die before I let anything happen to her.
这才是我想听的
That's what I wanted to hear.
因为她是我的家人
Because she's family, okay?
现在你也即将加入我们
And now you're gonna be family.
世界上最重要的莫过于家人
And there's nothing more important in the whole world than family.
这部电影一定很糟
That must have been one lousy movie.
这是我说的
That was me!
- 嗨   - 嘿 我可以跟你谈伴郎的事吗？
- Hi.    - Let's talk about this groomsman thing.
你选罗斯的话 他会安然陪你走完走道
If you pick Ross, he'll walk you down the aisle just fine.
可是你选我的话
But if you choose me...
你就有笑话听了
...you'll be getting some comedy.
虽然如此…
Even so...
我想我会选罗斯
...I think I'm gonna pick Ross.
让我告诉你该选我的原因
Let me tell you why you need to pick me.
好吧
Okay.
我小时候 总是受冷落
See, when I was a kid, you know, I was always left out of everything...
这让我很没有安全感
...and it really made me feel insecure.
体育课总是没人要我
I was always picked last in gym...
连那个不懂棒球规则的 胖交换学生都有人要
...even behind that fat exchange student who didn't know the rules to baseball.
那家伙被三振出局还往三垒跑
I mean, this guy would strike out and then run to third.
总之 如果我是唯一 无法参与婚礼的人
Anyway, if I'm the only one left out of this wedding...
那些不好的回忆一定又会涌上心头
...I just know that all those feelings are gonna come rushing back.
好吧 我选你
All right, fine, I pick you.
好极了
Yes!
伴郎钱德来也
Make "groom" for Chandler.
天啊
Oh, my.
不 照我的方式做 因为你的方式很蠢
No, we're gonna do it my way. Because your way is stupid.
好吧 我得挂了 我还有电话 牧师
All right, I got to go. I have another call, Reverend.
喂？
Hello?
- 很高兴我们谈开了   - 没错
- I'm glad we had this little talk.    - Yes.
谢谢你给我新婚之夜的指点
And thanks for all the wedding night advice.
我听完感到很自在
That didn't make me uncomfortable at all.
好吧 各位今晚见了
All right, so I'll see everybody tonight.
- 好   - 再见
- Okay.    - Bye.
你们知道走廊上有座大冰雕吗？
Did you guys know that there's a giant ice sculpture in the hall?
天啊 怎么会出现在这里？
PHOEBE: Oh, my God, what's it doing here?
看来他们把帐单地址 和送货地址搞混了
I guess it got sent to the billing address as opposed to the shipping address.
- 真是糟糕啊   - 天啊 每件事都乱成一团
- What a pickle.    - Oh, my God, everything's such a mess.
为什么会发生在我身上？
Why is this happening to me?
真想用舌头舔那东西
How bad do you wanna stick your tongue on that?
- 你好吗？ - 很好
- How's it going?    - Good.
我来买杯咖啡为婚礼待命
I'm just getting some coffee so I'm alert for the wedding.
我也是
That's what I was doing too.
祝你今晚愉快
Well, you have fun tonight.
- 你也是   - 我一定会
- You too.    - Oh, I will.
我也是
Me too.
等等 我知道我践的原因 你在践什么？
Wait a minute. I know why I'm being such an ass. Why are you?
- 我不能告诉你   - 我也不能告诉你
- I'm not supposed to tell you.    - I'm not supposed to tell you.
你答应我们俩都可以参与婚礼？
You told us both we could be in the wedding?
我意思是 你们不该告诉对方才对
In my defense, you weren't supposed to tell each other!
瑞秋 只有一个空缺 你必须选择
Rachel, only one of us can do it. You have to choose.
你我再续前缘
You and me together again.
瑞秋？敲敲门
Rach, Rach? Knock-knock.
- 是谁？ - 等婚礼上再跟你说
- Who's there?    - I'll tell you at the wedding.
我忘记拿围巾
Hey, I forgot my scarf.
我做不来 我不知道要选谁
I can't do this. I don't know which one of you guys to pick.
你还没决定吗？那好 我有个主意
Oh, you haven't picked yet? Oh, good, because I had an idea.
如果第三个伴郎由我家的狗 小胖担任会很有趣
I thought it would be fun if the third groomsman was my family dog, Chappy.
什么？狗？不行 决定权在瑞秋
What? A dog? No. Rachel gets to choose.
真是难以抉择
Wow, this is a tough one.
我想我要选狗
I think I'm gonna have to go with the dog.
等等 你是说厨师已经到了俱乐部
So, what you're saying is that the chef is at the Hamilton Club...
可是没食物？有饮料但酒保不见了？
...but the food is not? And the drinks are there but the bartender is not?
你开什么鬼玩笑？
Are you freaking kidding me?
还好吗？
How's it going?
- 救我   - 什么？
- Help me.    - What?
我要你恢复疯婆娘的角色
I want you to be crazy bitch again.
真的？
Really?
拜托
Please?
- 你真的要我回来？ - 比结婚还想
- You really want me to come back?    - More than I wanna get married.
各位 准备上工
Okay, people, we are back in business!
天啊 宝贝 我真想念你
Oh, God, I have missed you so much. Okay.
你去梳妆 其他的我来处理
Get your hair and makeup done. I'll take care of everything.
- 各位 我们该怎么办？ - 怎么了？
- Hey, what are you guys gonna do?    - About what?
暴风雪 我刚刚看了新闱
The blizzard. I just saw on the news...
这是20年来最严重的大雪
...it's the worst snowstorm in 20 years.
桥和隧道都关闭了
They already closed all the bridges and tunnels.
可是乐团和摄影师要从纽泽西赶来
But the band and the photographer are coming in from New Jersey.
我看是不能来了
I don't think they are.
看来你也别想参加婚礼了
Ha-ha! Looks like you're not gonna be in the wedding, either.
我很遗憾 菲比
So sorry, Pheebs.
- 俱乐部停电了 - 新闻说大部分地区都停电了
- Well, the club lost its power.    - The news said most of the city did.
- 你何时开始注意新闻的？ - 让我告诉你
- Since when do you watch the news?    - For your information...
自他们请到很辣的气象女主播开始
...since they hired a very hot weather girl.
真不敢相信你今天无法结婚
I can't believe you aren't getting married today.
我知道
I know.
外面好美 你不是一直很想在户外结婚？
It's so beautiful out there. You always wanted to get married outside.
- 干脆在街上举办婚礼   - 什么？
- Why don't you just do it on the street?    - What?
你看 雪差不多停了
Well, look, it's hardly snowing anymore.
这正好是最浪漫的场景
I mean, you couldn't ask for a more romantic setting.
也正好是你梦想中简单的婚礼
This could be the simple wedding you've always wanted.
你觉得如何？
What do you think?
我想今天把你娶进门
I think I wanna get married to you today.
我也是 摩妮卡 你觉得可行吗？
Me too. Monica, do you think we could do it?
可行
Affirmative!
把椅子搬过来
Okay, let's get these chairs out here!
阿甘 点亮圣诞灯
Gunther, hit the Christmas lights.
啊
Ah.
好 是谁把冰雕放在蒸气口的？
Okay, who left the ice sculpture on the steam grate?
- 麦克   - 你们来了 太好了 小胖
- Michael.    - Hey, you made it. Great. Chappy!
- 抱着   - 你好
- There you go.    - Hi. Hi.
妈 我知道在街上结婚你一定不认同
I know getting married in the street isn't what you approve of.
不 灯光和雪景很美 我看得爱不释手
No, it's lovely. The lights and the snow. I could look at them forever.
我在她的饮料里下了药
I crushed a pill and put it in her drink.
来吧 甜心
Come on, sweetheart.
小胖太小 在雪里走不动
You know, Chappy's too small to handle all this snow.
必须有人带着他走
Someone has to walk him down the aisle.
- 这个人可以算是参与婚礼？ - 应该算
- Would this person be in the wedding?    - I guess.
- 我来   - 我来
- I'll do it!    - I'll do it!
钱德 拜托 你不是怕狗吗？
Chandler, hello? I mean, aren't you scared of dogs?
我才不怕 我只要带着小胖…
I'm not scared. I'll just take little Chappy and...
他嗅得出我的恐惧 他咬得到我的脖子
He can sense my fear! My throat is exposed!
看来我能参加婚礼了
Well, I guess I'm in the wedding then.
他好臭
He stinks.
一级警戒 重复 一级警戒 这不是演习
Level one alert! I repeat, level one, this is not a drill!
出状况了 牧师被困在雪中无法赶来
We have a situation. The minister called. He's snowed in, he can't make it.
- 糟糕   - 别担心
- Oh, no.    - Hey, don't worry.
- 我还保有牧师的身份   - 真的？
- I'm still ordained from your wedding.    - Really?
我会傻到放弃牧师 免费搭地铁的特权吗？
Yeah. You think I'd give up being a minister and pay to ride the subway?
牧师不能免费搭地铁
Ministers don't ride the subway for free.
我认真读过《圣经》 没错 我们免费
I had to read the Bible pretty carefully, but, yeah, we do.
好 如果乔伊要主持婚礼 我们得找其他人陪菲比走走道
We have to find someone else to walk Phoebe down the aisle.
我可以
I'll do it!
好 麦克和乔伊就定位
Okay, Mike and Joey, get in position.
钱德 跟我来
Chandler, come with me.
好 乔伊要主持婚礼 由钱德陪你走
Okay, Joey's doing the ceremony, and Chandler's giving you away.
好 你好 新爸爸
Oh, okay. Hi, new Dad.
- 准备好了吗？ - 天啊 真的要成真了
- So you ready to do this?    - Oh, my God. This is really happening.
- 菲比 我真替你高兴   - 谢谢
- Uh-huh. I'm so happy for you, honey.    - Thank you.
我爱你 等等… 不能拥抱 会弄皱礼服
I love you. Wait, wait! No hugs! The dresses!
- 管他的   - 快来
- Oh, what the hell.    - Oh, come on.
- 我爱你们   - 我爱你
- I love you guys.    - I love you.
好 时间到 所有小队听我指示动作
Okay, it's zero hour! All teams execute on my count!
我们出动吧
Let's get this bad boy on the road!
今天晚上 你可以带耳机上床睡觉吗？
Is it okay I want you to wear that headset in bed?
2300时已安排了你裸体
I have you scheduled for nudity at 2300 hours.
太好了
Oh, yeah.
玛洁莉 奏乐
Okay, Marjorie, hit it.
- 天啊 罗斯 你该洗个澡的   - 是狗的味道
- Jeez, Ross. You could've showered.    - It's the dog.
伴郎？你站在这做什么？你的伴娘呢？
Groomsman? Why are you standing there? Where's your bridesmaid?
发生断箭状况 伴娘失踪
We've got a broken arrow! Bridesmaid down!
喔 是我
Oh, that's me.
- 准备好了吗？ - 好了
- Ready?    - Okay.
等等…
Oh, wait. Oh, no. Wait.
哇 你不冷吗？
Wow. Aren't you gonna be cold?
我不在乎
I don't care.
我可以充当我的"蓝色东西"
I'll be my "something blue."
- 你真美   - 谢谢
- You look beautiful.    - Thank you.
天啊
My God.
- 你不冷吗？ - 额
- Aren't you freezing?   - Nuh-uh.
各位亲朋好友
Friends. Family.
还有狗
Dog.
感谢各位前来见证这神圣的一刻
Thank you all for being here to witness this blessed event.
寒冷已侵袭至我的私处
The cold has now spread to my special place...
因此我就简短地说
...so I'm gonna do the short version of this.
菲比和麦克是天造地设的一对
Phoebe and Mike are perfect for each other.
我在此代表所有人
And I know I speak for everyone here...
预祝他们永浴爱河
...when I wish them a lifetime of happiness.
戒指在谁手上？
Who has the rings?
好的
Okay.
我的成长过程中 并没有正常的双亲
When I was growing up, I didn't have a normal mom and dad...
或是像大家拥有的正常家庭
...or a regular family like everybody else.
我一直觉得生命有所缺憾
And I always knew that something was missing.
但今天我站在这…
But now I'm standing here today...
我深深了解到我已拥有一切
...knowing that I have everything I'm ever gonna need.
你就是我的家人
You are my family.
菲比 你真是美丽动人
Phoebe, you are so beautiful.
你既仁慈又慷慨
You're so kind. You're so generous.
却也怪异得很
You're so wonderfully weird.
和你在一起的每一天都是场冒险
Every day with you is an adventure.
我无法置信自己有多幸运
And I can't believe how lucky I am.
我已等不及与你共度余生
And I can't wait to share my life with you forever.
等等 我忘了说…
Oh, wait! Oh, I forgot. And...
我爱你
...I love you.
还有你的眼睛真美
And you have nice eyes.
我也爱你
I love you too.
- 乔伊？ - 怎么了？
- Joey?    - Yeah?
小胖的心跳正在急速下降
Chappy's heart rate has slowed way down.
好的 菲比…
Okay. Phoebe...
你愿意接受此人为你的丈夫吗？
...do you take this man to be your husband?
我愿意
I do.
哦
Oh...
麦克 你愿意接受 此女为你的妻子吗？
Mike, do you take this woman to be your wife?
我愿意
I do.
我现在宣布你们为…
I now pronounce you...
正式夫妻
...husband and wife.
我结婚了
I got married!
谁拿件外套给我好吗？我快冷死了
Could someone get me a coat? I'm frigging freezing.
- 真是精彩的婚礼   - 的确
- It really was an incredible wedding.    - It was.
真希望不要结束 对了
I kind of don't want it to end. Hey...
你要进来喝一杯  吃点胸花吗？
...you wanna come in for a drink and a bite of corsage?
我很想 可是已经2300了
I'd love to, but it's 2300 hours...
我要去享受史无前例 最有组织化的性爱
...and I'm about to have the most organized sex anyone's ever had.
- 不错 罗斯到哪去了？ - 不知道
- Whatever happened to Ross?    - I don't know.
可能钓到那个跟他说话的辣妹
Maybe he hooked up with that hot girl he talked to.
快点 小胖 快办正事 拉
Come on, Chappy! Do your business! Make!
快拉
Make!
我真是自作孽不可活
I did not sign on for this.